[Music]
[音乐]
all right good welcome everybody I make
好的，我欢迎大家
that 11:30 so let's get started welcome
那11:30，所以让我们开始吧
great to see so many of you here for
很高兴见到你们这么多的人
this session about testing spring boot
本次有关测试Spring Boot的会议
applications my name is andy wilkinson I
我的名字叫安迪·威尔金森
work for pivotal where I spend most of
在我度过的大部分时间里为关键工作
my time working on spring boot I'm also
我在 spring boot 上工作的时间
the lead of spring rest Docs so before
Spring Rest Docs的主管如此
we kind of get into some of the lower
我们有点陷入低谷
level technical details of testing
测试级技术细节
spring boot applications I wanted to
我想要的 spring boot 应用程序
spend a little bit of time talking about
花一点时间谈论
why why do we bother testing at all it's
为什么为什么要打扰测试呢？
perhaps not the most glamorous part of
也许不是最迷人的部分
our jobs but I think it is one of the
我们的工作，但我认为这是其中之一
most important so a show of hands how
最重要的是举手示意
many of you here have tests that are
你们中的许多人的测试
automated and run without you having to
自动运行，无需您
do anything pretty much all of you
做几乎所有人
that's that's good to see and how many
那是很高兴看到的，有多少
of you have a situation where you can
你们中的一个人可以
commit to change some test run and then
承诺更改一些测试运行，然后
something pops out into a production
东西突然冒出来
environment at the other end of some
在另一端的环境
sort of deployment pipeline now it's
现在是一种部署管道
still pretty good ok great so why do we
还是不错，很好，那为什么我们要
bother testing at all well I think
我认为测试很麻烦
primarily we test to reduce risk that's
首先，我们进行测试以降低风险
what you should be looking to do when
你什么时候应该做什么
you're writing tests you're trying to
您正在编写测试，您正在尝试
allow the code that you've written to
允许您编写的代码
make its way successfully from your
成功地从您的方式
machine into a production environment so
机器进入生产环境
as lots of you appear to agree with
你们很多人似乎都同意
having those tests be automated and run
使那些测试自动化并运行
every time you make a change has big
每次您进行更改都很大
benefits because you know you get some
好处，因为你知道你得到一些
degree of assurance that when you've
保证的程度
made a change if it's passed those tests
通过了这些测试就做出了更改
that it's not going to go horribly wrong
不会犯错的
when it pops out the other end so I
当它弹出另一端时，我
think though it's important to think
想想虽然很重要
about things when you're adding tests
关于添加测试时的事情
why you're adding them and what that can
为什么要添加它们以及可以做什么
do in terms of reducing risk if you have
如果有的话，可以降低风险
no tests at all your risk is basically
根本没有测试的风险
as high as it can be and I think then
尽可能高，然后我想
the most important thing you can do is
您可以做的最重要的事情是
add the first test so in a spring boot
添加第一个测试，以便在 spring boot 中
application if you were only going to
如果您只想去申请
have one test a test that refreshes the
有一个测试可以刷新
application context already gets rid of
应用程序上下文已经摆脱
quite a lot of risk if you have one test
如果您进行一项测试，则会有很大的风险
that refreshes the context then you know
刷新上下文，然后您知道
hopefully that all of your beans are
希望你所有的豆子都是
available all of your dependency
可用你所有的依赖
injection will work your you know the
注射将起作用，您知道
web server will start etc etc but as you
网络服务器将启动等，但随着你
add more tests the benefit that you get
添加更多测试，您将获得好处
from adding those tests and the
从添加这些测试和
reduction in risk actually decreases and
风险降低实际上降低了，
it can be getting to cases where if
可能会遇到以下情况
you're blindly adding tests to your
您正在盲目地向您添加测试
application you're not really reducing
您并没有真正减少应用程序
the risk very much at all and this is
完全没有风险，这是
one area where I think that code
我认为该代码的一个领域
coverage can actually do more harm than
实际上，承保范围比
good how many of you pay attention to
好你们当中有多少人注意
code coverage numbers for your tests if
代码覆盖率测试
you take one thing away from this talk
你从这个谈话中拿走了一件事
I'd like you to start ignoring your code
我希望您开始忽略您的代码
coverage numbers or not treating them as
承保范围号或不将其视为
gospel I've worked in teams before where
福音我之前曾在团队中工作
you weren't allowed a code wasn't
您被禁止输入密码
allowed to kind of move on to the next
允许继续前进到下一个
stage until it was 80% code coverage you
直到达到80％的代码覆盖率
know 80% branch coverage or 80% line
知道80％的分支机构覆盖率或80％的线路
coverage whatever metric it was that
覆盖率是什么指标
they decided to focus on and you got
他们决定专注于
into this ridiculous situation where
陷入这种荒谬的境地
someone was at 79% code coverage and
某人的代码覆盖率为79％，
they just wanted their change to make it
他们只是想要自己的改变就能做到
into production or to the next stage so
投入生产或进入下一阶段
they'd add a test for a getter method
他们会为吸气剂方法添加测试
just to cover one more liner code and
只是为了覆盖另外一个班轮代码，
actually what are what is the chance of
其实有什么机会
you having made a mistake in a getter
你在吸气剂中弄错了
method it's probably zero or near to
方法可能是零或接近
zero so you've added that one more test
零，所以您又添加了一个测试
and you think oh the co-prophet coverage
你认为哦，先知的报道
has gone up risk has gone down it can
上升风险下降了可以
move to the next stage meanwhile
同时移至下一阶段
you could have a 50 line method that's
你可能有一个50行的方法
full of horrible complex logics that no
充满了可怕的复杂逻辑，没有
one really knows how to test or has
一个人真的知道如何测试或
bothered testing and that's just sitting
麻烦的测试，这只是坐
there untested you may have changed that
未经测试的你可能已经改变了
50 line method with all sorts of
50线的各种方法
branches in it and not bother testing it
在其中分支，而无需进行测试
but because you added a test for a
但是因为您添加了一个测试
getter your untested code was allowed to
得到你未经测试的代码被允许
kind of move along to the next stage of
进入下一阶段
the pipeline so code coverage can kind
管道，因此代码覆盖范围可以
of be a guy
成为一个男人
to tell you you know some tests have run
告诉您您已经进行了一些测试
and some methods were executed but I
和一些方法被执行，但我
think you need to you need to look more
认为你需要你需要多看
into detail about what has been covered
详细介绍已涵盖的内容
and not pay too much attention just to
而不是只注意
the percentages that Co coverage
公司覆盖率
provides you I think the other important
提供你我认为另一个重要
thing when you're thinking about your
想着自己的事情
tests is to embrace the fact that
测试就是要接受这样一个事实：
realistically you are never going to
实际上，您永远不会
reduce the risk to zero it doesn't
将风险降低到零
matter how many tests you write things
不管你写多少次测试
are still going to go wrong in a
仍然会出错
production environment and so I think
生产环境，所以我认为
there needs to come a point where you
需要到达一个点
ask yourself is it worth adding any more
问自己是否值得再增加一点
tests is it worth writing a complex test
测试是否值得编写复杂的测试
that scaffolds a complex environment and
搭建一个复杂的环境
maybe say it's a problem that only
也许说这只是一个问题
happens under very high load or with
发生在非常高的负载或
certain you know concurrent conditions
确定您知道并发情况
you could try and recreate that for
您可以尝试重新创建
example in a staging environment and
在暂存环境中的示例
then have some regression test suite
然后有一些回归测试套件
that tries to replicate that workload
试图复制该工作负载
where this thing one time went wrong in
这件事曾经错在哪里
production I think you'll end up
生产，我想你会结束
spending more time keeping that staging
花更多的时间来保持这一阶段
environment vaguely in sync with
与环境模糊地同步
production then you'll you'll gain from
生产，那么您会从中受益
perhaps avoiding that problem recurring
也许避免再次出现该问题
in production I think you have to accept
在生产中，我认为你必须接受
at some point that things are going to
在某些时候，事情将会发生
go wrong and so you should stop
出问题了，所以你应该停止
investing your time in writing more
花时间写更多
tests and think about instead investing
测试并考虑转而投资
time in making your production
制作时间
environment more observable so when
环境更可观察，所以什么时候
things go wrong in production you get
生产中出现问题
metrics out of it you get logs out of it
从中获取指标，从中获取日志
you get whatever you like out of it that
你会从中得到想要的东西
lets you quickly pinpoint something's
让您快速查明某事
gone wrong wrong in production and
在生产中出错
quickly identify what went wrong and
迅速找出问题所在，
then hopefully push a fix or roll back
然后希望推动修复或回滚
to a previous state so another thing
回到以前的状态，另一件事
that you can do not always appropriate
你不能总是合适的
for all sorts of problems but being able
对于各种问题，但能够
to roll back to a previous known good
回滚到以前的已知商品
state can also be beneficial so if you
状态也可能是有益的，所以如果你
push something into production and your
将某物投入生产，您的
test didn't catch the problem and all
测试没有发现问题，所有
hell breaks loose you've got two choices
地狱破了你有两个选择
one is you try and fix it but that can
一个是您尝试修复它，但是可以
be stressful if your service isn't
如果您的服务不愉快，请保持压力
available and that's critical for your
可用，这对您至关重要
bill
法案
those conditions aren't ideal to be
这些条件并不理想
trying to make a change because
试图做出改变，因为
presumably you made a mistake when you
想必您在您犯错时
weren't under pressure and now if you
现在没有压力，如果你
are under pressure trying to fix this as
面临着试图解决此问题的压力
quickly as possible the chances of you
尽快给你机会
making another mistake are quite high so
犯另一个错误的可能性很高
if you've invested time in being able to
如果您投入时间来
roll back then that might have been a
回滚，那可能是
better investment than spending more
比花更多的钱更好的投资
time writing complex kind of system
时间写作复杂的系统
integration type tests and I think when
集成类型测试，我认为什么时候
you're writing tests you should also
您正在编写测试，还应该
think about the sort of mistakes that
考虑一下那种错误
you make and this will vary from team to
您所做的，这将因团队而异
team so the people painting the the
团队，使人们绘画
school writing on this road they
他们在这条路上的学校写作
obviously they were good with colors
显然他们的色彩很好
they got all the letters the same color
他们得到所有字母相同的颜色
but not so good with spelling you'll
但是拼写不好
know in your team the sort of mistakes
知道你团队中的错误
that you make and in your domain the
您所做的并在您的域中
sort of things that you often get wrong
经常出错的事情
and that's where the risk lies and
那就是风险所在，
that's where code coverage can be
那是代码覆盖范围所在
misleading because not all lines are
误导，因为并非所有行都
equal and if it's a common mistake that
相等，如果这是一个常见错误，
you individually make or that you know
您个人做出或您知道
members of your team makes then that's a
您团队中的成员使
good place for you to focus your
您集中精力的好地方
attention when you're writing your tests
在编写测试时要注意
rather than again just kind of being
而不是只是被
concerned with I need to hit a certain
有关我需要打一定
code coverage percentage all right so
代码覆盖率可以吗
that's hopefully kind of level set
希望这是一个水平设置
things a bit about why we write tests
关于为什么我们编写测试的一些事情
and how I kind of think about the sort
以及我如何思考那种
of tests that we should be writing and
我们应该编写的测试
when perhaps we should stop writing
也许什么时候我们应该停止写作
tests and I want to start talking about
测试，我想开始谈论
the actual testing side of a spring boot
spring boot 的实际测试面
application and I think a good place to
应用程序，我认为一个好地方
start a place where a lot of people
建立一个很多人的地方
start is with unit tests and really if
首先是单元测试，如果
your unit testing a spring boot
您的单元测试 spring boot
application you're not actually testing
您尚未实际测试的应用程序
a spring boot application at all your
一个Spring Boot应用程序
individual units should have very little
个别单位应该很少
if anything to do with spring or spring
如果与春天或春天有关
boot and this is something you know back
启动，这是您知道的东西
in whenever it was 2003 or so spring
在2003年左右的春天
boot sorry spring framework got an awful
启动对不起Spring框架有一个可怕的
lot of traction because it let you write
很多牵引力，因为它可以让您写作
code as plain old java objects it we
作为普通的旧Java对象的代码，我们
moved away from the then Java to j2ee
从当时的Java移至j2ee
way of doing things where you had to sub
做事的方式
class things so if you'd written an EJB
对事物进行分类，如果您编写了EJB
it was very difficult to test it without
没有它很难测试
kind of all the scaffolding that an EJB
EJB的所有支架
container gave you and spring let you
容器给了你，春天让你
just write a plain old java object that
只是写一个普通的旧Java对象
you could then test very easily just in
然后，您可以轻松地进行测试
a standard unit test without having to
标准单元测试，而无需
worry about having an EJB container or a
担心拥有EJB容器或
servlet container or whatever may it be
servlet容器或其他可能的容器
and that holds true you know word like
这是真的，你知道像
fifteen sixteen years later and I think
15年后的16年，我认为
that still holds true now but you can
现在仍然成立，但您可以
get quite a lot of mileage out of just
不仅获得了很多里程
writing unit tests for your application
为您的应用程序编写单元测试
testing individual units now some people
现在测试一些个人单元
don't like unit tests and think that you
不喜欢单元测试，以为你
should write more kind of functional
应该写更多的功能
tests because they consider the unit
测试，因为他们考虑了单位
tests to be difficult to evolve you know
测试很难发展，你知道
if you rewrite a chunk of your
如果您重写了大部分
application then you've got all these
应用程序，那么您已经拥有了所有这些
unit tests that then also need to be
然后还需要进行单元测试
rewritten and I think I have some
改写，我想我有一些
sympathy for that argument and I'm not
同情这个说法，我不是
really sure that there's anything right
真的确定一切正确
or wrong here but it is something to be
还是错在这里，但这是有可能的
aware of with the sort of test that
知道那种测试
you're writing that if they are reducing
你写的是，如果他们减少
risk presumably you want to keep them so
冒着风险，您可能想保留它们
as you evolve your application you're
当您开发应用程序时，
going to want to evolve the tests as
想要发展为
well so when you're writing tests you
好吧，当您编写测试时，
want to be thinking about writing them
想考虑写他们
in a way you know you want them to be as
以某种方式，您知道您希望他们成为
concise as possible so that hopefully
尽可能简明扼要
they are not to contain consuming for
他们不包含消费
you to evolve as your application
您随着应用程序的发展而发展
evolves that may mean for you that unit
可能对你意味着那个单位的发展
tests are fine that may mean for you
测试很好，可能对您意味着
that you have a few unit tests and you
你有一些单元测试，你
focus more on functional tests just
只专注于功能测试
something to think about in your team
在团队中要考虑的事情
what works best for the sort of
什么最适合那种
application that you're writing another
您正在编写另一个应用程序
thing as I was preparing this talk I saw
我在准备这次演讲时看到的东西
this tweet come past and I think
这条推文过去了，我想
actually I put this in the unit test
实际上我把它放在单元测试中
section but I think it applies for
部分，但我认为它适用于
everything for all your tests is when
所有测试的一切都在何时
you're naming your tests don't call them
您正在命名测试，不要称呼它们
like test1 test2 test3
像test1 test2 test3
because future you will hate past you
因为未来你会讨厌过去
when that test fails and you're looking
当该测试失败并且您正在寻找
at it and you're trying to remember what
在它，你试图记住什么
on earth it was that you were testing
在地球上，那是你在测试
something like that just isn't going to
这样的事情只是不会
help so use whatever naming convention
帮助使用任何命名约定
you like here but just use something
你喜欢这里，只是用点东西
that says you know when X is in
那说你知道X在什么时候
why should happen bass try and describe
为什么要发生低音尝试并描述
in the name of the test what it is that
以测试的名义是什么
the test is is checking and you can do
测试正在检查，您可以执行
this you know in a variety of ways if
您可以通过多种方式知道这一点
you're just writing you know if you're
你只是在写，你知道你是否
using j-unit for you can just put it in
使用j-unit可以将其放入
the test method if you're using J unit 5
如果使用的是J单元5，则为测试方法
then there's a new display name
然后有一个新的显示名称
annotation which lets you you know you
使您了解自己的注释
can stick a more human readable name in
可以在其中粘贴更易读的名称
an annotation rather than it happened to
注释，而不是碰巧
try and reverse engineer it from the
尝试从
method name and just I would encourage
方法名称，只是我会鼓励
you to think about your names and maybe
你想想你的名字，也许
adopt a convention across your team so
在整个团队中采用惯例
that everybody in the team uses the same
团队中的每个人都使用相同的
style for the test method names so that
测试方法名称的样式，以便
if someone else in your team comes to
如果您团队中的其他人来
look at a test that you've written or
查看您编写的测试或
vice versa that you can just look at the
反之亦然，你可以看看
name of the test and you can get a rough
测试的名称，您可以大致了解
idea of what the test is supposed to be
测试应该是什么的想法
checking so that if the test is broken
检查以确保测试不合格
or you're trying to change some code
或者您正在尝试更改一些代码
that the test exercises and the test
测试练习和测试
starts failing while you're doing that
在这样做时开始失败
you can figure out have I made a mistake
你可以找出我犯了一个错误
or was the test wrong or is there have
还是测试错误或有
the the criteria changed as a result of
由于
the modifications that you've made so
您所做的修改
imagine here that we've got a typical
想象这里我们有一个典型的
application or subset of an application
应用程序或应用程序的子集
and we have a bunch of beans that have
我们有一堆豆子
relationships between them so some of
他们之间的关系
these beans have dependencies some of
这些豆有一些依赖
them don't I think some of these are
他们不认为其中一些是
better candidates for unit testing than
比单元测试更好的候选人
others so all these here that are
其他人，所有这些都是
highlighted in green they don't have any
以绿色突出显示，他们没有任何
dependencies so for me these are ones
依赖关系，对我来说，这些都是
that if you are of a mind to unit test
如果您打算进行单元测试
they are great candidates to write unit
他们是写单元的好人选
tests for you're not going to have to
无需为您进行测试
mock anything you're not going to have
嘲笑你不想要的任何东西
to scaffold anything you can just
脚手架
exercise the logic and make sure that
运用逻辑并确保
with particular inputs you get the right
通过特定的输入，您可以获得正确的选择
output if you look at these components
如果您查看这些组件，则输出
these have dependencies so if you want
这些有依赖关系，所以如果你想
to test these you're probably going to
要测试这些，您可能要
have to mock something if you want them
如果你想要的话，一定要嘲笑
to be true unit tests you're going to
成为真正的单元测试
have to mock something out so if you're
必须嘲笑一些东西，所以如果你是
a Java developer you're probably using
您可能正在使用的Java开发人员
maketo I think that's generally what we
我认为这通常是我们
recommend for spring boot users it's
推荐给Spring Boot用户
what spring boot test provides
Spring Boot测试提供了什么
and people have mixed opinions about how
人们对如何
many people here use mops in their tests
很多人在测试中使用拖把
how many of you avoid mocks like the
你们当中有多少人避免像
plague all one person so um again I
再次困扰所有人
don't think there's any right or wrong
不要以为是非
here essentially when you start mocking
从本质上讲，当您开始嘲笑时
something you have an extra
你有一些额外的东西
implementation of something to behave to
实现某种行为
maintain so when you've written
保持这样，当你写
[Music]
[音乐]
expectations against your mark and you
对你和你的期望
say you know when this particular method
说你知道什么时候这个特殊的方法
is is called rapport return this value
被称为融洽返回此值
or throw this exception or whatever may
或抛出此异常或任何可能
happen and you need to keep that
发生，你需要保持
behavior that you've mocked out in sync
您已同步嘲笑的行为
with the actual implementation that's
与实际的实现是
going to be subbed in in a more you know
将被嵌入更多你知道的
in a functional test or when the
在功能测试中或
application is actually running in
应用程序实际上正在运行
production so there's an extra kind of
生产，所以有一种额外的
onus on you as a developer to keep
您作为开发人员的责任
things up to date and you could get into
最新的事情，你可以进入
a situation I'm sure you've all seen it
我确定你们都看过这种情况
where your expectations you've set up on
您设定的期望
the mock diverge from how the service
模拟与服务的方式有所不同
actually behaves so your unit tests all
实际表现良好，因此您的单元测试了所有
pass and then maybe you run a functional
通过，然后也许您运行了功能
test and everything breaks or then maybe
测试，一切都坏了，或者也许
something pops out into production and
东西突然冒出来生产
everything breaks because your mock and
一切都中断了，因为您的模拟和
your actual service got out of sync so
您的实际服务不同步，所以
you need to be careful and generally
您需要注意并且通常
speaking assuming you may know Tet and
假设您可能知道Tet和
mo mistakes when you write the test the
在编写测试时可能会犯错
behavior you set up on the mocks are
您在模拟中设置的行为是
really just a point in time statement
真的只是一个时间点
saying the thing I'm tested behaved like
说我测试的东西表现得像
this at the time that I wrote the test
在我编写测试时
you then need to remember to keep
然后您需要记住保持
reviewing that and if someone else
审查，如果有人
changes the behavior of the thing that
改变事物的行为
you've mocked out you also need to try
你已经嘲笑了，你还需要尝试
and remember to review the expectations
并记得回顾期望
you set up and any marks to make sure
您设置了任何标记以确保
that they're kept in sync another
他们保持同步
component that we have here so is here's
我们在这里拥有的组件在这里是
something that's talking to a server so
与服务器对话的东西
imagine that this is something that's
想象这是
talking using rest template it would be
谈论使用其余模板
a typical example in a spring app or web
Spring应用程序或Web中的典型示例
client for example and these can kind of
例如客户，这些可以
these can be interesting components to
这些可能是有趣的组成部分
test you often don't have any choice but
测试你通常别无选择
to mock something out you might be in a
嘲笑你可能在
situation where the live serve
现场服务的情况
this actually calls in a production
这实际上需要生产
environment just isn't available to you
环境对您不可用
in your test environment or maybe you
在您的测试环境中
can kind of get a staged version of the
可以得到一个分阶段的版本
service that you could call but you
您可以打电话给您的服务，但是您
often don't have any choice about
常常没有选择
calling the the actual real-world system
调用实际的实际系统
for example we've got something a little
例如，我们有一些东西
app that we use to you in the spring
我们在春季为您使用的应用程序
team to keep track of our release
团队跟踪我们的发布情况
calendar and it goes off and looks at
日历，它熄灭，看着
github milestones and collects all the
github里程碑并收集所有
information about all the release dates
有关所有发行日期的信息
for all of the projects so that thing is
对于所有项目而言，
talking to github github has rate limits
与github交谈github有速率限制
so when we're running the tests we
因此，当我们运行测试时，
either have to be very careful not to
要么必须非常小心，否则
exceed github rate limits without
超过github速率限制而没有
authenticating or we can have some
进行身份验证，否则我们可以有一些
credentials that we use which then
我们使用的凭证
raises the rate limits but then we have
提高了速率限制，但是我们有了
to worry about in our tests we've got to
担心在我们的测试中，我们必须
provide those credentials somehow and
以某种方式提供这些凭据，并
then you get into well then my test
然后你进入健康然后我的测试
suite doesn't want to have those secrets
套房不想拥有这些秘密
checked into open - you know it's an
签入开放-您知道这是一个
open source project we don't want to
我们不想的开源项目
have those checked in to get we then and
有那些签入让我们然后
it all just gets more and more
这一切变得越来越多
complicated so what you can do instead
很复杂，所以您可以做些什么
is you can use something to mock out the
你可以用一些东西来模拟
service that you're calling and how many
您正在呼叫的服务以及多少
of you here have heard of mock rest
你们当中有人听说过模拟休息
service server not many so this is a
服务服务器不多，所以这是一个
hidden gem of the spring test module and
弹簧测试模块的隐藏宝石和
what it does is it lets you basically
它的作用是让您基本上
set something up and you can say when I
设置一些东西，你可以说什么时候我
receive a request with this particular
收到与此特定的请求
HTTP verb and maybe these request
HTTP动词，也许这些请求
parameters or whatever this is the
参数或任何这是
response that I want you to return so
我要你回来的回应
you can set up expectations at the HTTP
您可以在HTTP上设置期望
level about how you want this thing to
关于你想要这个东西的程度
behave and then you can bind rest
表现出来，然后你就可以约束休息
template to it so rather than you doing
模板而不是你做
something like so rest template as you
像这样的休息模板
may know implements the rest operations
可能知道执行其余操作
interface so you could take an approach
界面，因此您可以采取一种方法
where you mock out the rest operations
在这里模拟其余的操作
interface and then you set up a bunch of
界面，然后您设置了一堆
expectations using mojito to say when
期望用莫吉托说什么时候
there's a get for entity call with this
有一个与此实体通话
URI and you know these this request
URI，您知道这些请求
entity this is the response entity that
实体，这是响应实体，
you should return
你应该回来
but that misses out quite a lot of the
但这错过了很多
the things that your service is actually
您的服务实际上是
going to do at run time if you're
如果您要在运行时执行
mocking out the rest operations
模拟其余的操作
interface you could make a mistake in
界面中您可能会犯错
the URI that you pass in you could make
您传递的URI可以使
a mistake in how you're substituting
您如何替换的错误
path variables into the URI your HTTP
路径变量到HTTP的URI中
message conversion might not be quite
消息转换可能不完全
right if you use something like mock
对，如果您使用类似模拟的东西
rest service server you can take your
休息服务服务器，您可以将您的
rest template bind it to the mock rest
休息模板将其绑定到模拟休息
service server and then interact at the
服务服务器，然后在
HTTP level so you get some almost for
HTTP级别，因此您几乎可以获得
free you get testing that the rest
免费获得其余的测试
template calls that you are making are
您正在进行的模板调用是
actually mapping to the URI that your
实际映射到您的URI
service operates at so if you're like
服务的运营时间是
when we were dealing with github we
当我们与github打交道时
could basically take the github API
基本上可以采用github API
documentation and the expected format of
文档和预期的格式
requests and response payloads and map
请求和响应有效负载及映射
that on to mock rest service server and
模拟休息服务服务器
then it gives us a higher degree of
那么它给我们更高的程度
confidence that our rest template is
相信我们的休息模板是
making the right course to the to the
正确地走向
actual HTTP back-end if you're not using
实际的HTTP后端（如果您未使用）
rest template and you're using web
休息模板，而您正在使用网络
client instead the story isn't quite the
客户反而故事不尽如人意
same there is not yet support for using
同样，尚不支持使用
web client with mock rest service server
带有模拟休息服务服务器的Web客户端
there is an open issue in the spring
春天有一个未解决的问题
framework issue tracker to add that
框架问题跟踪器添加
support and I think it's in the five dot
支持，我认为这是五个点
X backlog so we might see it in a future
X待办事项列表，因此我们将来可能会看到
5 to X release with Spring Framework but
5到X用Spring Framework发布，但是
in the meantime you can do something
在此期间您可以做点什么
very similar with okay HTTP mock web
与HTTP仿冒网站非常相似
server so as you may know ok HTTP is
服务器，所以您可能知道确定，HTTP是
another HTTP client on the JVM but it
JVM上的另一个HTTP客户端，但是
has a mock web server that it provides
有一个提供的模拟Web服务器
and there isn't coupled to ok HTTP and
而且还没有确定的HTTP和
the spring framework team I believe I'm
我相信我是 Spring Framework 团队
right in saying use this for testing web
说对了，用它来测试网站
client themselves so they have web
客户自己，所以他们有网络
client test and they set up the mock web
客户测试，他们建立了模拟网站
server and in much the way I as I
服务器以及我作为我的方式
described for mock rest service server
描述为模拟休息服务服务器
you can set up the expectations on the
您可以对
mock web server so you can say you know
模拟Web服务器，所以您可以说您知道
when you get a get request to this URI
当您收到对此URI的获取请求时
return this respond
返回此回复
when you receive a post request with
当您收到发帖请求时
this payload then return this response
该有效载荷然后返回此响应
and you have control over the response
并且您可以控制响应
body and the status code and all sorts
主体和状态代码以及各种
of things so it allows you to do testing
的东西，所以它可以让您进行测试
of your HTTP clients at the HTTP level
HTTP级别的HTTP客户端数量
which is really what you care about that
你真的在乎那个
they're making the right HTTP requests
他们正在做出正确的HTTP请求
and handling the HTTP responses properly
并正确处理HTTP响应
without having to worry about the kind
不用担心那种
of the nitty-gritty exactly you know the
确切的说，你知道
Java calls that you're making that
Java调用您正在做的
result in those HTTP requests being made
导致发出这些HTTP请求
another piece to look at is imagine that
另一个要看的是想象
you have something that's doing some
你有正在做的事
data access and there can be times here
数据访问，这里可能会有时间
where you don't you're not in a position
你不在那里你不在一个位置
to call the actual real live data base
调用实际的实时数据库
you probably don't want to be so say for
你可能不想这样说
example you have some spring data
例如你有一些 spring data
repositories so they're kind of an
存储库，所以它们有点像
interesting case because in some cases
有趣的情况，因为在某些情况下
very simple crud cases you don't really
非常简单的杂案
write very much code you just have a an
写很多代码，你只有一个
interface that you have written that
您编写的界面
extends JP a repository or crud
将JP扩展为存储库或Crud
repository or what have you in spring
仓库或春季您有什么
data and then spring data actually looks
数据，然后弹簧数据实际上看起来
at your interface and the methods the
在您的界面和方法
names of the methods and generates the
方法名称并生成
appropriate queries that should then be
然后应该是适当的查询
run against what data ever data backends
与数据后端的数据冲突
you're using for standard crud stuff you
您正在使用标准杂物
may just be able to get away with
也许可以逃脱
mocking out that repository interface
模拟该存储库接口
you know there's a maybe there's a
你知道那里可能有一个
findall method that doesn't take any
无需任何费用的findall方法
arguments and just returns a list of
参数并返回一个列表
person that's probably fine
可能还不错的人
you could mock that out with maketo and
你可以用maketo模拟出来
drop that in there and there's very
放到那里，那里非常
little risk that you know you'll find
知道自己会发现的风险很小
all method is going to be there's going
所有方法都会存在
to be a mistake in it if there is it's
如果有的话就是一个错误
going to be in spring data because you
将会出现在 spring data 中，因为您
haven't written anything for the find
没有为发现写任何东西
all that's a standard method on the crud
所有这些都是生硬的标准方法
repository interface if you get into the
存储库界面（如果您进入
business of writing more complex methods
编写更复杂方法的业务
so for those that you don't know spring
所以对于那些你不知道春天的人
data lets you write queries either in
数据使您可以在
the method names or you can also provide
方法名称，或者您也可以提供
additional metadata that let you create
其他可让您创建的元数据
queries so you could write a method name
查询，以便您可以编写方法名称
that's like find all where age is
就像找到年龄所在的所有地方
greater than 10 and it will turn that
大于10，它将变成
into the appropriate query to make in
进入适当的查询
the the datastore whichever one you're
数据存储区中的任何一个
using be it a an SQL based datastore or
使用基于SQL的数据存储区还是
a no SQL date based data store there's
没有基于SQL日期的数据存储
support for both and from the interface
同时从界面支持
and kind of the query levels there for
还有那里的查询级别
the purposes here they they are the same
他们在这里的目的是相同的
if you're doing that and you've started
如果您这样做并且已经开始
to write your own queries either by
通过编写自己的查询
providing additional methods or by
提供其他方法或通过
providing metadata with via annotations
通过注释提供元数据
then you're into the realms of being
那么你就进入了被存在的境界
able to make mistakes and there's more
能够犯错误，还有更多
risk and at that point I don't think you
冒险，那时候我不认为你
want to be mocking out the interface you
想嘲笑你的界面
need to do you need to do something else
需要做你需要做其他事情
which we'll talk about in a moment and I
我们稍后会谈到，我
think JDBC template is in a similar boat
认为JDBC模板在类似的船上
how many of you use JDBC template still
仍有多少人仍在使用JDBC模板
a reasonable number
一个合理的数字
yeah it's perfectly good if you're
是的，如果你
writing you know if you're don't want to
写你知道你是否不想
use an ORM and you have some SQL queries
使用一个ORM，你有一些SQL查询
to make JDBC template is still a really
使JDBC模板仍然是一个真正的
really good option how many of you have
真的好选择，你们有多少人
tested your database code by mocking out
通过模拟测试数据库代码
JDBC operations one person two people oh
JDBC操作一人二人哦
three the problem I think with doing
我认为做的三个问题
that is that the chance that you make a
那就是你创造一个机会
mistake in your query is too high so if
您的查询中的错误过高，因此如果
you mock out JDBC operations and then
您模拟出JDBC操作，然后
you just set up expectations you might
你只是建立期望，你可能
have made a typo in your query you might
在查询中输入错误，您可能
have got column name wrong you might
列名错误，您可能会
have put a bracket in the wrong place
将支架放在错误的位置
you might have forgotten to quote
你可能忘了报价
something and if you just mock out JDBC
东西，如果您只是模拟JDBC
operations rather than actually sending
操作，而不是实际发送
that text as a query to the database
该文本作为对数据库的查询
you're not going to find out until
直到你才发现
something does actually exercise that
确实有锻炼
query against the real database be that
针对真实数据库的查询是
in a test later on or be at once it's
在以后的测试中或马上进行
popped out of your deployment pipeline
从您的部署管道中弹出
and is and is running in production so a
并且正在并且正在生产中，因此
common solution to this problem is to
解决此问题的常见方法是
use an in-memory database in your tests
在测试中使用内存数据库
so you could use h2 you could use hsqldb
所以你可以使用h2你可以使用hsqldb
as a replacement typically some
作为替代品
applications you might use an in-memory
您可能会在内存中使用的应用程序
database that might be sufficient
可能足够的数据库
depending on the applications
取决于应用
persistence needs but I think that's
持久性需求，但我认为那是
very much the exception rather than the
非常例外，而不是
rule so you could drop in h2 you could
规则，以便您可以加入h2
drop in hsqldb as a replacement but then
放入hsqldb作为替换，然后
you get into then there's some risk
你进入那会有一些风险
where is h2 or is hsqldb gonna behave in
h2或hsqldb在哪里运行
exactly the same way as my back end and
和我的后端完全一样
h2 has some compatibility mode so for
h2具有一些兼容模式，因此对于
example you can run it in Postgres
您可以在Postgres中运行它的示例
compatibility mode where it pretends to
假装为兼容模式
behave like a Postgres database so there
表现得像Postgres数据库，所以
are things behavior that is specific to
是特定于事物的行为
Postgres and h2 kind of tries to emulate
Postgres和H2尝试模仿
that and behave in the same way and
并以相同的方式表现
that's good up to a point where if that
在某种程度上，这是很好的
compatibility isn't in sync with the
兼容性与
version of Postgres that you're using
您使用的Postgres版本
then you can almost get lulled into a
那么你几乎会陷入沉迷
false sense of security thinking I've
我对安全思想的错误认识
tested this using h2 in Postgres
在Postgres中使用h2对此进行了测试
compatibility mode all my SQL is
兼容模式我所有的SQL都是
absolutely fine and then you actually
绝对很好，然后你实际上
find out when you point a real Postgres
找出何时指向真正的Postgres
instance that it's not fine and your
实例，那不好，你
queries start to break so I think when
查询开始中断，所以我认为什么时候
that happens you need an alternative
发生这种情况，您需要替代方法
option and one that I think is really
选项，我认为这是真的
really good is a project called test
一个很好的项目叫做测试
containers how many of you have heard of
容器你们中有多少人听说过
test containers okay about half so for
测试容器可以一半左右
those of you that haven't test
那些还没有测试的人
containers is an open source project
container是一个开源项目
that uses docker and docker containers
使用docker和docker容器
to stand up so in this case you can
站起来，在这种情况下，您可以
basically you can run it can stand up
基本上你可以运行它可以站起来
anything that's in a docker container
码头集装箱中的任何东西
anything that you can package up in a
您可以打包的所有内容
docker container test containers will
docker容器测试容器将
help you use in your tests but a typical
帮助您在测试中使用，但通常
usage and the one I want to talk about
用法和我想谈的一个
here is for it to stand up an actual
这是它站起来的实际
genuine instance of Redis or a genuine
Redis的真实实例或真实的
instance of Mongo or my sequel or
Mongo或我的续集或
whatever datastore you are using test
您正在使用的任何数据存储测试
containers can help you and it provides
容器可以为您提供帮助
integration with J unit 4 via a rule and
通过规则与J单元4集成
J unit 5 fire and extension 2
J单元5消防和扩展2
basically allowed you to say in your
基本上可以让你在
test I want Redis please and it will go
测试我想要Redis，它会走
off and as long as you have docker
只要有码头工人就可以
running on your machine it will go off
在您的机器上运行它将消失
and you can point it to a particular
您可以将其指向特定的
docker image for Redis so that could be
Redis的docker映像，因此可能是
one just from docker hub just the
仅来自docker hub的一个
standard Redis images on docker hub or
docker hub上的标准Redis映像或
it could be any docker image it could be
它可以是任何docker镜像
one of your own creation whatever you
属于您自己的创作之一
need and it will then when your test
需要，它将在您进行测试时
runs it will start up that container for
运行它将为该容器启动
you and then provide you with very easy
然后为您提供非常简单的方法
access to the hostname and port that you
访问您的主机名和端口
need to use to communicate with Redis
需要使用与Redis进行通信
running in that container and then you
在那个容器中运行，然后你
can run or you know it doesn't have to
可以运行，或者您知道它不必
be Redis whatever data store then you
成为Redis的任何数据存储，然后您
can run your test against that data
可以针对该数据进行测试
store sure that it is in a known good
存放在已知货品中
state because it's a fresh docker
状态，因为它是一个新鲜的码头工人
container every time so you don't have
每次都有容器，这样您就不用了
to worry about other tests having
担心其他测试
polluted the database or left things in
污染了数据库或遗留了东西
a broken State things will be exactly as
一个破碎的国家，事情将完全一样
they were left when the docker image was
他们在docker映像被保留时被留下了
created either by a third-party if it's
由第三方创建（如果是）
on a public docker hub or that you've
在公共docker hub上或者您已经
created downside is that the docker
造成的不利之处是码头工人
story and Windows doesn't work quite so
故事和Windows无法正常工作
well but if you're on Mac or Linux I
很好，但是如果您使用的是Mac或Linux，我
would thoroughly recommend checking out
会彻底建议退房
something like test containers and I
像测试容器之类的东西
personally so in spring boots codebase
亲自如此在 spring boot 代码库中
in fact we have Auto configuration for
实际上，我们为
there's a an embedded Mongo project
有一个嵌入式Mongo项目
which kind of tries to do a similar
哪种尝试做类似的
thing and if you're using spring boots
的东西，如果您使用 spring boot
testing support and you have the
测试支持，您就可以
embedded Mongo dependency on the class
对类的嵌入式Mongo依赖
path then spring boots testing support
路径然后 spring boot 测试支持
will Auto configure embedded Mongo but
将自动配置嵌入式Mongo，但是
the name embedded Mongo it's kind of a
嵌入式Mongo这个名字有点像
it's a bit of a misnomer it's not really
这有点用词不当，不是真的
embedded it's not embedded in the JVM
嵌入它不是嵌入在JVM中
and which your tests are running what it
以及哪些测试正在运行
really means is it's going to grab hold
真的意味着它将抓住一切
of a Mongo binary start it up on your
一个Mongo二进制文件在您的计算机上启动它
machine and then you can in a similar
机器，然后你可以在一个类似的
way you can get a port to access that
您可以获取端口来访问该端口的方法
Mongo instance and then you can run your
Mongo实例，然后您可以运行
tests against this genuine real world
针对这个真实的现实世界进行测试
Mongo instance and that's great because
Mongo实例，这很棒，因为
you're actually testing against Mongo
您实际上是在对Mongo进行测试
rather than some mocked variant of Mongo
而不是蒙戈的一些嘲讽变体
and I think there are projects for some
我认为有一些项目
of these data stores that
这些数据存储中
try to mock them and pretend to be the
尝试嘲笑他们并假装自己
actual real thing but that has some of
实际的真实事物，但是有一些
the same problems of using h2 or hsqldb
使用h2或hsqldb的相同问题
in kind of in compatibility mode where
在兼容模式下
you might get slightly different
您可能会略有不同
behavior for things like embedded Mongo
嵌入式Mongo之类的行为
because it doesn't run in a docker
因为它不在docker中运行
container it's running so if you're a
容器正在运行，因此如果您是
Windows developer you will be running
您将要运行的Windows开发人员
Mongo on Windows whereas in production
Windows上的Mongo，而在生产中
you might be running on Linux so you've
您可能正在Linux上运行，因此您已经
got operating system differences whereas
有操作系统差异，而
if you're running your tests in a docker
如果您正在docker中运行测试
container you can get or running the
您可以获得或运行的容器
server the backend service that you're
服务器您的后端服务
talking to the data store or whatever it
与数据存储或其他任何数据通信
may be if you're running that in a
可能是因为您正在
docker container the chances are that
码头集装箱的机会是
you can get closer to your production
您可以更接近您的生产
environment so you could perhaps use the
环境，所以您也许可以使用
exact same Linux distribution on the
完全相同的Linux发行版
same version of the Linux kernel in the
相同版本的Linux内核
docker container that your production
您生产的docker容器
environment is running on so it just
环境正在运行，所以它只是
helps to reduce the risk a little bit by
有助于通过以下方式降低风险
aligning what you're testing against
调整要测试的内容
more closely with what is running in
与正在运行的内容更加紧密
your production environment all right so
您的生产环境还可以
that's kind of unit testing and kind of
这是一种单元测试，
the gray area between a pure unit test
纯单元测试之间的灰色区域
and something where you start mocking
还有你开始嘲笑的东西
things out and you start worrying about
事情出来，你开始担心
about databases but all of those that
关于数据库，但所有那些
you can do all those sorts of tests you
你可以做所有这些测试
can do without starting an application
无需启动应用程序即可完成
context so you can test JDBC template or
上下文，以便您可以测试JDBC模板或
a components use of JDBC template as
组件使用JDBC模板作为
long as you're injecting that template
只要您注入该模板
into the component you can you can test
可以测试的组件中
it quite easily you can mock it out if
它很容易就可以模拟出来，如果
you want to you can configure it to talk
您想要的话，可以配置它进行通话
to test containers by giving it a data
通过提供数据来测试容器
source with a particular URL if you're
带有特定网址的来源（如果您是
testing rest template you don't need an
测试其余模板，您不需要
application context you can just bind it
您可以将其绑定到应用程序上下文中
to the mock rest service server and
到模拟休息服务服务器，并
inject that into your component but I
注入到您的组件，但我
now want to move on and talk about
现在想继续谈论
integration test so this is where you're
集成测试，这就是您要去的地方
actually starting up an application
实际启动一个应用程序
context so this is where your
上下文，这就是你的地方
application as a whole or part of your
整个或部分应用程序
application has all been tested and
应用程序都已经过测试，
spring gets involved the dependencies
春天参与了依赖
are being injected etc
正在注射等
so as I suspect almost all of you know
所以我怀疑几乎所有人都知道
the main entry point into spring boots
spring boot 的主要切入点
testing is the spring boot test
测试是 spring boot 测试
annotation we also have annotations for
注解我们也有注解
slice tests but if you're doing a
切片测试，但是如果您正在
full-blown integration test in the
全面的集成测试
spring boot world you will be using
您将使用的 spring boot 世界
spring boot test and spring boot test
弹簧启动测试和弹簧启动测试
hooks into and builds on top of the
钩入并建立在
testing framework in spring framework to
在Spring框架中测试框架
provide you with kind of a spring boot
为您提供一种 spring boot
specific testing experience so it's the
具体的测试经验
use of spring boot test that means that
使用弹簧启动测试意味着
you get kind of all of the standard
您得到所有​​标准的一种
spring application behavior that mimics
模仿的Spring应用程序行为
what you get in your main method when
当你在主要方法中得到什么
you run your application so you get you
您运行您的应用程序，以便获得
know the configuration property binding
知道配置属性绑定
from spring boot you get the application
从 spring boot ，您可以获得应用程序
property support and all those sorts of
财产支持以及所有这些
things are what come by using spring
事情是春天带来的
boot tests to kind of customize the
引导测试以自定义
behavior of Springs test framework now
Springs测试框架的行为
I'm going to get kind of quite down into
我将深入了解
the details of exactly how the test
确切的测试细节
framework works because some spring boot
框架之所以有效，是因为一些 spring boot
tests specific features build quite
测试特定功能相当不错
heavily upon some kind of lower-level
在某种较低级别上
parts of Springs test framework and one
Springs测试框架的一部分和一个
of those is context caching so what I
这些是上下文缓存，所以我
want to hopefully do here is to give you
希望在这里做的就是给你
all an understanding of how Springs test
对Springs测试的所有理解
framework caches context and when you
框架缓存上下文以及何时
will see a context being reused and when
将看到上下文被重用，以及何时
you will see a particular test class
您将看到一个特定的测试课程
creating a new application context so
创建一个新的应用程序上下文
here we have a typical integration test
这里我们有一个典型的集成测试
that you might you know you've probably
你可能知道你可能已经
all seen something very similar to this
所有人都看到与此非常相似的东西
so this is a J unit for example so the
所以这是一个J单位，例如
first annotation we come to is run with
我们要使用的第一个注释
spring runner and so this is telling J
春季赛跑者，所以这告诉J
unit to pass over control to spring
单元将控制权移交给弹簧
framework to test framework to run the
框架测试框架运行
test we've then got the spring boot test
测试，然后我们进行了 spring boot 测试
annotation so this is spring boot saying
注解，这就是Spring Boot所说的
to the test framework spring frameworks
到测试框架spring框架
test framework that this needs to be a
测试框架，它必须是
spring boot style test we've then got an
spring boot 样式测试，然后
active profiles annotation which is part
活动配置文件注释是一部分
of spring test framework so this is
春季测试框架，所以这是
tuning the profiles that are active for
调整活动的配置文件
when you are running a particular test
当您运行特定测试时
so this is building on the profile
所以这是建立在个人资料上
specific beam support or kind of
特定的梁支撑或种类
configuring profile specific beam
配置配置文件专用梁
support and then we've got test property
支持，然后我们有测试属性
source which is another annotation from
来源，这是来自的另一个注释
spring framework to test framework but
春天的框架来测试框架，但
lets you provide a property source so
让您提供属性来源
I'm pointing here to a properties file
我在这里指向属性文件
and then those properties are going to
然后这些属性将
be contributed to the environment and
为环境做出贡献
then spring boots configuration property
然后 spring boot 配置属性
binding will be able to use those
绑定将能够使用那些
properties as a source so you can use it
属性作为来源，因此您可以使用它
to tune things customized configuration
调整事物自定义配置
specifically for your tests speaking
专为您的口试
about the environment and customizing it
关于环境并对其进行自定义
you can see here I'm using the
您可以在这里看到我正在使用
properties attribute on spring boot test
Spring Boot测试中的properties属性
so this is another way of configuring
所以这是另一种配置方式
properties and you've you only got one
属性，而你只有一个
or two and you don't want to separate
一两个你不想分开
them out into a separate file you can
将它们放入单独的文件中，您可以
use the properties attribute on spring
在spring上使用properties属性
boot test and it does exactly the same
开机测试，它做的完全一样
thing it adds a property source to to
它向其添加属性源的东西
the environment so here we're enabling
环境，所以我们在这里启用
JMX for this particular test the key
JMX为此特定测试的关键
thing with all of will almost all of
几乎所有的东西
these annotations is that they have an
这些注释是因为它们具有
effect on the beans that will be present
对将要存在的豆类的影响
in the application context so spring
在应用程序上下文中如此春天
boot test active profiles and test
引导测试活动配置文件和测试
property sauce can all affect beans that
调味酱都会影响豆类
appear in the
出现在
so spring boot test is the thing that
因此， spring boot 测试就是
turns it into a a test of a spring boot
把它变成 spring boot 的测试
application so it gives you
应用程序，它给你
configuration property binding but it
配置属性绑定但是
also the crucial thing that it does is
它所做的关键是
it controls the configuration class
它控制配置类
that's used as likely source for all of
被用作所有
your applications configuration so when
您的应用程序配置，以便何时
you have spring boot test on a test
您在测试中进行了 spring boot 测试
class we go off looking for a class
下课我们去找课
annotated with spring boot application
用Spring Boot应用程序注释
so you'd only have your spring boot
所以你只有 spring boot
application on your main class more
在您的主班上申请更多
accurately we're actually looking for a
准确地说，我们实际上正在寻找
class annotated with spring boot
用 spring boot 注释的类
configuration but that's a meta
配置，但这是一个元
annotation on spring boot application so
在Spring Boot应用程序上的注释
typically in your app what we're doing
通常在您的应用中我们正在做什么
here is going off looking for spring
这里要去寻找春天
boots application on a class and we look
在一个类上启动应用程序，我们看一下
up the package hierarchy so if your
包的层次结构，所以如果您
tests are in common example fubar we'll
测试是常见的示例fubar
look in that package and then we'll go
看看那个包裹，然后我们去
up to comm example foo and then up to
到comm example foo，然后到
comm example until we find a class in
通讯示例，直到我们在
your main code that is annotated with
您的主要代码带有注释
spring boot application and that is the
spring boot 应用程序，那就是
class that we'll use as kind of the
我们将使用的类
source for how your application is going
您的应用程序进行情况的来源
to be configured so if it's annotated
进行配置，以使其带有注释
with spring boot application that means
使用Spring Boot应用程序意味着
spring boots Auto configuration will be
spring boot 自动配置将
switched on because that's another meta
打开，因为那是另一个元
annotation on spring boot application so
在Spring Boot应用程序上的注释
that obviously that can have a huge
那显然可以有一个巨大的
effect on the beans in your application
对应用程序中的bean的影响
context because you've switched on Auto
上下文，因为您已打开自动
configuration so spring boots Auto
配置，使 spring boot 自动
configuration is going to contribute the
配置将有助于
beans to your context there's also
豆到您的上下文中也有
active profiles if you enable some
活动配置文件，如果您启用了一些
profiles if you activate some profiles
个人资料（如果您激活了一些个人资料）
in your test and you have profile
在测试中，您拥有个人资料
specific beans those beans depending on
那些豆取决于具体的豆
whether they're either the profile that
他们是否是个人资料
they belong to is active will or will
他们所属的是主动意志还是意志
not be part of the context there's also
不是上下文的一部分，还有
test property source it can change the
测试属性源，它可以更改
properties that are in the environment
环境中的属性
and if your code or some auto
如果您的代码或某些自动
configuration that you are using has
您正在使用的配置
used conditional on property to control
使用基于条件的条件来控制
the presence or absence of certain beans
是否存在某些豆类
then the test property source and the
然后是测试属性来源和
properties that provides can also affect
提供的属性也会影响
the beans that are in the application
应用程序中的bean
context similarly with the properties
上下文与属性类似
attribute on spring boot test anything
spring boot上的属性测试任何东西
that manipulates the environment
操纵环境
and have an effect on beans that appear
对出现的豆有影响
in the context there are a couple of
在上下文中有几个
more and a couple more annotations that
越来越多的注释
you can use as well that can affect the
您也可以使用会影响
context so you can use import to import
上下文，以便您可以使用import导入
other configuration classes you can also
您还可以使用其他配置类
use context configuration which is
使用上下文配置
another way of providing the
提供
configuration class that's going to
将要使用的配置类
configure the context for your tests so
配置测试的上下文，以便
when you're writing your tests you need
在编写测试时，您需要
to think about all of these different
考虑所有这些不同
things that are controlling and
控制和
affecting the beans that appear in the
影响出现在
in the context when the test framework
在上下文中测试框架
is running a test and it accounts as a
正在运行测试，它占
new a new test class when j-unit
当j-unit时新建一个新的测试类
encounters a new test class it talks to
遇到与之交谈的新测试班
spring boots talks to the test framework
spring boot 与测试框架对话
tells it to run the test and the test
告诉它运行测试和测试
framework goes off and looks at all of
框架开始运作，并研究所有
these sources for being configuration
这些用于配置的资源
and figures out which beans are going to
并弄清楚哪些豆子要去
be in the context and it creates a cache
在上下文中并创建一个缓存
key based on all of that configuration
基于所有配置的密钥
and only when the cache key matches a
并且仅当缓存键与
previous test will the context be reused
先前的测试将重用上下文
so if you subtly change the
因此，如果您巧妙地更改
configuration such that you've got one
配置，使您拥有一个
more bean or one fewer beans then you'll
多一点或少一点豆，你就会
find that the test framework will start
发现测试框架将开始
a new context for you rather than
为您而非您提供新环境
reusing an old one so if you're running
重用旧的，所以如果您正在跑步
your spring boot test suite and you find
您的 spring boot 测试套件，您会发现
you know you've got lots and lots of
你知道你有很多
integration tests and you find that
集成测试，您会发现
things are slower than you would like
事情比你想的要慢
one thing to look at is how many
要看的一件事是多少
application context are being created
正在创建应用程序上下文
and there's logging support that you can
并且有日志记录支持，您可以
turn on in the test framework if you set
如果您设置，请在测试框架中打开
all spring framework tests to debug
所有Spring框架测试以进行调试
logging it will output information for
记录它会输出信息
you about cache hits and misses and
关于缓存命中和未命中以及
things and it can help you to identify
事物，它可以帮助您识别
problems or little optimizations you
问题或很少的优化
could make to perhaps share
可以分享
configuration across tests so that the
跨测试进行配置，以便
application context can be reused
应用程序上下文可以重用
whether or not that's a problem really
这是否真的是一个问题
depends on how big your application is
取决于您的应用程序有多大
and how long it takes the context of
以及需要多长时间
refreshed so it'll vary depending on the
刷新，因此会有所不同，具体取决于
size of the application that you're
您正在使用的应用程序的大小
working on
从事
there will also be cases where the
在某些情况下，
context cashier you actually
你实际上是上下文收银员
deliberately don't want the context to
故意不希望上下文
be cashed you may have a test that has a
兑现您可能有一个测试
side effect that leaves the context or
留下上下文的副作用或
something in the context dirty so that
在上下文中有些脏的东西
it's not in a clean state and we want
它不是处于干净状态，我们想要
our tests to be able to run without
我们的测试能够在没有
having side effects on other tests we
对其他测试有副作用
don't want to write tests that need to
不想编写需要
be run in a particular order because it
以特定的顺序运行，因为它
can lead to strange problems where you
可能导致您遇到奇怪的问题
run a little one bit of the test suite
运行一点测试套件
and everything passes and then you run
一切都过去了，然后你跑
the whole thing and something fails all
整个事情和所有事情都失败了
the ordering changes because in theory
顺序发生变化，因为理论上
you know the ordering isn't guaranteed
你知道不能保证订购
to always be exactly the same so you
总是一样，所以你
might have something that for example
可能有一些东西，例如
changes the in-memory state of one of
更改其中之一的内存状态
your beans the dirties context can help
您的豆类脏物上下文可以提供帮助
you with that because you're basically
你这样，因为你基本上是
saying to the test framework don't cache
对测试框架说不要缓存
the context for me I know that this is
对我而言，我知道这是
going to leave the context in a bad
会使上下文陷入困境
state and any other subsequent test even
状态和其他任何后续测试
if it uses the same configuration it
如果使用相同的配置
needs a new context so now that you've
需要一个新的上下文，所以现在您已经
hopefully got an understanding of how
希望对如何
the context caching works I wanted to
我想要的上下文缓存工作
talk to you a bit about slice test
与您谈谈切片测试
support in spring boots how many of you
spring boot 支持你们
are familiar with test slices in spring
熟悉春季的试片
boot okay cool so we have a bunch of
引导好酷，所以我们有一堆
annotations in spring boot in the spring
春天的 spring boot 中的注释
boot test auto configure module that
引导测试自动配置模块
gives you support for testing a
为您提供测试支持
particular slice of your application so
您的应用程序的特定部分
you can see here we've got ones for
你可以在这里看到我们有
various data backends so spring data
各种数据后端，所以弹簧数据
LDAP spring data JPA
LDAP弹簧数据JPA
as bring data Redis etc we've also got a
带来数据Redis等，我们还有一个
slice for web related tests whether
与网络相关的测试切片
you're using spring MVC there's web MVC
您正在使用Spring MVC，有Web MVC
test whether using web flux there's web
测试是否使用网络流量来检测网络
flux test rest client tests do tests
流量测试其余客户测试做测试
various things that you might want to
您可能想做的各种事情
test and what this lets you do is homed
测试，这使您可以做的事
in on a particular aspect a particular
在一个特定的方面
slice of your application rather than
应用程序的一部分，而不是
testing the whole thing and it does that
测试整个事情，并做到这一点
via component scan filtering so when
通过组件扫描过滤，所以当
your application starts up and you're
您的应用程序启动，您正在
using component scanning and we go off
使用组件扫描，我们开始
looking at the clasp
看着扣
earth to find all of your components the
地球找到您所有的组件
slice test add a filter to that
切片测试为此添加了一个过滤器
component scanning process so we remove
组件扫描过程，因此我们将其删除
beans that aren't relevant to the
与
particular slice that you're testing so
您正在测试的特定切片
for example if you're testing some data
例如，如果您正在测试一些数据
JPA stuff then you don't really care
JPA的东西，那么你真的不在乎
about your web controllers so we can
关于您的Web控制器，以便我们可以
exclude all of those from the test and
从测试中排除所有这些并且
just focus on the data JPA part so to
只关注数据JPA部分，以便
give you a concrete example of this here
这里给你一个具体的例子
we have a kind of an example application
我们有一个示例应用程序
so we have spring boot application on
所以我们有 spring boot 应用程序
our main application class sitting in
我们主要的应用程序类别
one package and then we have two
一个包，然后我们有两个
packages one for customers and one for
为客户打包一个，为客户打包一个
orders and in each we've got some web
订单，在每个订单中我们都有一些网站
stuff and in this case some JPA stuff so
的东西，在这种情况下，一些JPA的东西，所以
we've got interfaces that extend JPA
我们有扩展JPA的接口
repository if we use data JPA tests and
如果我们使用数据JPA测试和
what happens via the component scan
通过组件扫描会发生什么
filtering is that we get rid of the
过滤是我们摆脱了
controller's so now when you're setting
控制器的设置现在是这样
up your environment you're not paying
不用付钱的环境
the cost of those controllers being
这些控制器的成本是
created during application context
在应用程序上下文中创建
refresh or indeed any of their
刷新或什至确实
dependencies all that will be in the
依赖所有将在
context are the JPA repositories and
上下文是JPA存储库，
then the JPA infrastructure upon which
然后是JPA基础架构
they depend so we'll bootstrap the data
他们取决于，所以我们将引导数据
source and hibernate and your JPA
源和休眠以及您的JPA
repositories and that's about it
仓库，就是这样
everything else will have been filtered
其他所有东西都会被过滤掉
out similarly if you write a web MVC
如果您编写Web MVC，也会有类似的结果
test
测试
what kind of will do the other side of
另一面会怎样
it we'll get rid of all of your JPA
它会摆脱您所有的JPA
stuff so you will no longer pay the cost
东西，所以您将不再支付费用
of bootstrapping hibernate when you just
引导休眠时，您只是
want to test your web layer all you'll
想要测试您的Web层
get are your controllers and all of the
得到您的控制器和所有
JPA stuff datasource hibernate etc will
JPA东西数据源休眠等将
all be filtered out now a problem that
现在都被过滤掉了
this creates is or something that you
这创造的是或你
need to do when this happens for data
发生这种情况时需要做的数据
JPA it's probably fine because it's it's
JPA可能很好，因为它是
kind of at the bottom of your dependency
有点依赖
graph and your data JPA repositories are
图和您的数据JPA存储库是
kind of leaf nodes in the graph in terms
图中叶节点的种类
of your code you're not going to be
您的代码不会
injecting any dependencies into them but
向它们注入任何依赖关系，但是
for your controllers they probably call
他们可能会为您的控制器打电话
another service or they
其他服务或他们
be calling a spring data repository or
正在调用spring数据存储库或
something so you need to provide
一些东西，所以你需要提供
something to them for them to interact
给他们一些互动的东西
with you know it's they're going to have
与你知道这是他们将要
some dependencies that need to be
一些需要的依赖
injected and that is where mock bean and
注入，这是模拟豆和
spy bean come in so you can see here
间谍豆进来，所以你可以在这里看到
imagine that we have customer controller
想象我们有客户总监
integration tests with web MVC tests on
Web MVC测试上的集成测试
it so I'm saying I just want to test my
所以我说我只是想测试我的
web layer I'm injecting my customer
Web层我正在注入客户
repository into the test because I want
因为我想要存储库到测试中
to sell back some behavior on it before
卖回之前的一些行为
I exercise my controller and I've also
我锻炼我的控制器，我也
had to provide a separate configuration
必须提供单独的配置
class to provide mocks of the customer
类提供客户的模拟
repository and the order repository and
仓库和订单仓库，以及
there's a lot of ceremony here it gets a
这里有很多仪式
bit clunky you have to set up all these
有点笨拙，您必须设置所有这些
mocks so you can replace this with the
模拟，因此您可以将其替换为
use of mock bean instead so this
使用模拟豆代替所以
configuration here is essentially
这里的配置本质上是
equivalent to the previous there's no
相当于以前没有
longer any need for that static in a
不再需要任何静态
class that's mocking the customer
嘲笑客户的课程
repository and order repository instead
仓库和订单仓库
these fields are annotated with mock
这些字段使用模拟注释
bean are found by spring boots testing
spring boot 测试发现豆
support and we will either replace a
支持，我们将替换
customer repository being in the context
客户资源库在上下文中
of there is one already or will add one
已经有一个或将添加一个
to it so you now have a customer
为此，您现在有了一个客户
repository or order repository that you
您的存储库或订单存储库
can then set the bare expectations up on
然后就可以设定任何期望
in your test and then you can exercise
在测试中，然后您就可以锻炼
your controller using mock MVC or
您的控制器使用模拟MVC或
whatever you like and check that given
无论你喜欢什么，并检查给定的
certain responses from the repository it
来自存储库的某些响应
does the the expected things there's
是否有预期的事情
still something though that's not quite
仍然有些东西，虽然那不是很
right with this that I don't really like
我真的不喜欢
and we've got customer repository where
我们有客户资料库
customer controller tests customer
客户总监测试客户
repository but we've also got order
仓库，但我们也有订单
repository and that's wrong I don't like
仓库，那是我不喜欢的错误
that I imagine that your custard of
我以为你的蛋ust
domain shouldn't know anything about the
域不应该对
order domain or vice versa but because
订购域，反之亦然，因为
these this code is in separate packages
这些代码在单独的程序包中
and because we need all of our
因为我们需要我们所有的
controllers are going to exist in the
控制器将存在于
context because we've sliced out
上下文，因为我们已经切出
everything other than controllers and
除了控制器和
web related stuff
网络相关的东西
you still need to provide a mocked order
您仍然需要提供模拟订单
repository and that means you can't make
仓库，这意味着你不能
your order repository interface package
您的订单存储库界面包
private so you've now just for testing
私人的，所以您现在仅用于测试
purposes you've had to increase the
目的，你不得不增加
visibility of some of your api which
您的某些api的可见性
introduces the risk of package tangles
引入包装缠结的风险
or people calling things across parts of
或人们在各地呼叫事物
your domain when they shouldn't do so
您的网域，当他们不应该这样做时
what we'd really like to get to is where
我们真正想去的地方是
we only need to mock out the customer
我们只需要嘲笑客户
repository to test our customer
测试我们的客户的资料库
controller and what we can do to help
控制器以及我们可以提供的帮助
with that is that we can say to web MVC
就是说我们可以对网络MVC说
test I want you to focus just on a
测试我想让你专注于
specific controller so I don't want you
特定的控制器，所以我不要你
to focus on all of the controllers but
专注于所有控制器，但
just focus on this one controller now
现在就专注于这个控制器
you should think about this but also
你应该考虑一下
have in your back of your mind the
在你的脑海中
things that I mentioned about context
我提到的有关上下文的事情
caching if you are focusing on a
如果您专注于
specific controller and just web MVC
特定控制器和Web MVC
that's really narrowed down the beans
确实缩小了豆子的范围
that are in the context you're going to
在上下文中，您将要
get kind of the basic web infrastructure
了解基本的Web基础架构
that's needed by mock MVC so you'll get
这是模拟MVC所需的，因此您将获得
like the mock dispatch a servlet but
像模拟派遣一个servlet但
you'll just get that one controller so
你只需要一个控制器
if you write another test for your order
如果您为订单编写另一个测试
controller and you focus right in on the
控制器，您就可以专注于
order controller you're going to get
您将获得的订单控制器
another context there's not going to be
另一个环境将不会
an opportunity for the the context cache
上下文缓存的机会
to reuse that context so there's a
重用该上下文，所以有一个
trade-off to be made here it should be
需要在此处进行权衡
the case and in our experience it
这个案例，根据我们的经验
generally is the case that because
通常是因为
you're focused in on one specific
你专注于一个特定的
controller the time to refresh that
控制刷新时间
application context is minimal because
应用程序上下文是最小的，因为
it's got so little in it so the benefits
它很少，所以好处
that you get in terms of code visibility
就代码可见性而言
and the ability just to focus
和专注能力
specifically on what you want to test in
特别是要测试的内容
our experience outweigh the cost of
我们的经验超过了成本
creating the extra context because they
创建额外的上下文，因为它们
are so quick to be recreated to be
很快被重新创建
created sorry but it is something to
造成了抱歉，但这是要
bear in mind as you embrace the slice
拥抱时切记
testing support to think about the
测试支持以考虑
effect that it can have on context
它可以对上下文产生的影响
caching because it does affect the beans
缓存，因为它确实会影响bean
that are in the context
在上下文中
just got a couple of minutes left now so
现在只剩几分钟了
the last thing I want to mention was J
我最后要提的是J
unit 5 unfortunately this talk was
不幸的是，第5单元
yesterday so I can't ask you all to go
昨天，所以我不能要求大家走
to Sam's talk later today but what I can
今天晚些时候去山姆的谈话，但我能
say is I would thoroughly recommend
说是我会彻底推荐
checking out the recording on YouTube
在YouTube上查看录音
after the after the conference J unit 5
会议J单元5之后
is particularly relevant now for spring
现在对春季特别重要
boot users that finally at long last
引导用户终于终于
we've wanted to do this for at least one
我们至少要这样做一次
minor release if not two in spring boot
弹簧释放，如果不是两个，则较小释放
2.2 spring boots test will give you J
2.2 spring boot 测试会给你J
unit 5 by default rather than J unit 4
默认情况下，单元5而非J单元4
so there's loads of goodies in J unit 5
所以J单元5有很多东西
the display name stuff that I talked
我说过的显示名称的东西
about nested test classes there's all
关于嵌套测试类
sorts of stuff in there the new
新的东西在那里
extension model does loads of those good
扩展模型可以很好地完成这些工作
stuff check out Sam's talk to learn more
查看Sam的谈话以了解更多信息
about it in a recording and when you
在录音中以及当您
upgrade to spring boot 2.2 you will be
升级到Spring Boot 2.2，您将
using J unit 5 by default but and the
默认情况下使用J单元5，但
thing that's delayed us in doing this
拖延了我们这样做的事情
while we've been waiting for the Maven
当我们一直在等待Maven的时候
support to be ready is that the way
准备好就是这样
we've configured J unit 5 in spring boot
我们已经在 spring boot 中配置了J单元5
test means that your J unit 4 tests will
测试意味着您的J单元4测试将
continue to run on top of J unit 5
继续在J单元5上运行
without you having to change any code so
无需更改任何代码，因此
you can migrate to J unit 5 whenever
您可以随时迁移到J单元5
you're ready or you can stick with the J
您已经准备好，或者可以坚持使用J
unit 4 API
单元4 API
running on top of the J unit 5 test
在J单元5测试之上运行
execution engine and that's done via the
执行引擎，这是通过
vintage engine that is part of J unit 5
属于J单元5的老式引擎
that as far as your code is concerned
就您的代码而言
let's it pretend to be j unit 4 so you
让我们假装成j单元4，所以你
can continue to use j unit 5 and migrate
可以继续使用j单元5并进行迁移
it's continue to join you at 4 and
它会继续加入您的4和
migrate to j unit 5 as it makes sense to
迁移至第5个单元，
do so that it's not going to be a big
这样做不会太大
bang switch when you upgrade to spring
升级到春季时爆炸开关
boot 2.2 and that's all I had
启动2.2，这就是我所拥有的
thank you very much for your time
非常感谢您的宝贵时间
everybody I hope you found that useful
希望大家都觉得有用
and I think we're out of time but I'll
我认为我们没时间了，但我会
be out in the hall so if you have any
在大厅外面，如果有的话
questions and you want to come up and
问题，你想提出来，
ask me or you see me around the rest of
问我还是在其他地方看到我
the day in the conference please come up
会议当天请来
and ask me any
问我任何
that you've got thank you very much
非常感谢你
everybody
大家
[Music]
[音乐]